Judith Raskin Papers, 1911-2000
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES V. AUDIOTAPES 1959-1978, undated
  - Reel-to-Reel
    - 11 May 1975: Mahler--"Rheinlegendchen," "Ich atmet' einen linden Duft," "Wo die schönen Trompeten blasen," and "Wer hat dies Liedlein erdacht?"; Schubert--"Die Forelle"; Brahms--"Lullaby", Martin Isepp, piano, Master's School Theatre, Dobbs Ferry, NY (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - 11 Jan 1976: An all Beethoven program in memory of Ceil R. Mann, Raskin and the Beaux Arts Trio (Menachem Pressler, piano; Isidore Cohen, violin; Bernard Greenhouse, cello), Town Hall, NYC (program enclosed) (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - 20 Jun 1978: Selections from Debussy, Mahler and Schubert, Martin Katz, piano, 1978 Art Song Festival, Westminster Choir College, Princeton, NJ (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - 20 Jun 1978: Selections from Barber, Rorem, Laderman, Schubert, and Mendelssohn, Martin Katz, piano, 1978 Art Song Festival, Westminster Choir College, Princeton, NJ (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Cassette tapes
    - n.d.: Mendelssohn/Mahler (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - n.d.: Bach--Easter Oratorio, Philadelphia Orchestra, Eugene Ormandy, conductor (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - n.d.: Miriam Gideon (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - n.d.: Mozart--The Impresario (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - n.d.: Hugo Weisgall (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - n.d.: Bach--Jauchzet Gott; Mozart--"Exsultate Jubilate" (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - n.d.: Maureen Lehane, Pergolesi--Stabat Mater (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - n.d.: Side a: Mozart--Requiem, Cleveland Orchestra; and Bruckner--Te Deum; 30 Sept 1965 - interview, Martin Perlich (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - n.d.: Side b: Judith Raskin/Daisy Ford tape exchange (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - n.d.: Cleveland Orchestra: Berlioz--"Les Nuits d'été" (Pierre Boulez, conductor); Mozart--Requiem (George Szell, conductor) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Phonograph record: Smith College Glee Club, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 10)